=The Shoufu Can Read Mind=
= الشوفو يستطيع قراءة العقل =
=Episode 8=
= الحلقة 8 =
We
نحن
couldn't gather so much gold for now.
لا يمكن جمع الكثير من الذهب في الوقت الحالي.
Don't worry.
لا تقلق.
My father is a general.
والدي هو جنرال.
He's worth 3,000 taels of gold.
إنه يساوي 3000 تايل من الذهب.
Take him with you.
خذه معك.
Shut up.
اسكت.
Do you think I'm a butcher
هل تعتقد أنني جزار
and you're actually negotiating?
وأنتم تتفاوضون بالفعل؟
Don't kill me.
لا تقتلني.
We've given you the money.
لقد قدمنا ​​لك المال.
Kill him first.
اقتله أولا.
Shut up.
اسكت.
What did you make me press my thumbprint on?
ماذا جعلتني أضغط على بصمة إبهامي؟
This is the evidence that you colluded with Sir Zhou
هذا هو الدليل على تواطؤك مع السير زو
to cheat
للغش
on the imperial examination.
في الامتحان الإمبراطوري.
I'll just need to report this to the magistrate
سأحتاج فقط لإبلاغ القاضي بذلك
and Shen family is done.
وانتهت عائلة شين.
Who are you?
من أنت؟
Where is my sister?
أين أختي؟
Where are you hiding my sister?
اين تختبئين اختي؟
Don't worry.
لا تقلق.
We're robbers with dignity.
نحن لصوص بكرامة.
We won't harm a little girl.
لن نؤذي فتاة صغيرة.
Let's go.
دعنا نذهب.
Father.
أب.
Will our whole clan be sentenced to death?
هل سيحكم على عشيرتنا كلها بالموت؟
Talk to me.
تحدث معي.
What should I say?
ماذا يجب أن أقول؟
What else should I say?
ماذا علي أن أقول؟
You're useless.
أنت عديم الفائدة.
I should ask you instead. Are you even my father?
يجب أن أسألك بدلا من ذلك.  هل انت حتى ابي؟
If it wasn't for you, a useless son,
إذا لم يكن لك أيها الابن عديم الفائدة ،
why would I look for Sir Zhou?
لماذا أبحث عن السير زو؟
I'll beat you.
سأهزمك.
Father.
أب.
Yanqing?
يانكينغ؟
What are you doing here?
ما الذي تفعله هنا؟
Madam.
سيدتي.
Miss Shen is back safely.
الآنسة شين عادت بأمان.
Mother!
الأم!
Huan!
هوان!
- It's good that you're fine. - Mother!
- من الجيد أنك بخير.  - الأم!
I was so worried.
انا كنت قلقا جدا.
Mother,
الأم،
what could've happened to me?
ماذا يمكن ان يحدث لي
Weren't you kidnapped?
ألم تختطف؟
Your father and Le went to redeem you.
ذهب والدك ولو ليخلصوك.
They have yet to come home.
لم يعودوا إلى المنزل بعد.
What?
ماذا؟
So,
لذا،
the kidnappers
الخاطفين
got the evidence of you colluding with Sir Zhou
حصلت على الدليل على تواطؤك مع السير زو
by saying that they kidnapped Huan?
بقولهم أنهم خطفوا هوان؟
No.
لا.
We're not colluding with him.
نحن لا نتواطأ معه.
It's not that serious.
ليس الأمر بهذه الخطورة.
Father.
أب.
Le.
ال.
You're really muddle-headed.
أنت حقًا مشوش الذهن.
His Majesty has noticed that
لقد لاحظ جلالة الملك ذلك
Sir Zhou always leaks
دائما ما يتسرب السيد تشو
the exam questions
أسئلة الامتحان
and ordered me to investigate in private.
وأمرني بالتحقيق على انفراد.
It's just that I didn't know
كل ما في الأمر أنني لم أكن أعرف
you both are in it.
كلاكما فيه.
I wanted
أنا أردت
to buy the questions for Le,
لشراء الأسئلة لـ Le ،
but
لكن
the questions
الأسئلة
are sold at 100 taels of silver.
تباع في 100 تايل من الفضة.
I
أنا
couldn't bring myself to buy it.
لم أستطع إحضار نفسي لشرائه.
Father,
أب،
so you didn't want to pay for it.
لذلك لا تريد أن تدفع ثمنها.
Zhihuan is worth 3,000 taels of gold.
تبلغ قيمة Zhihuan 3000 تايل من الذهب.
I'm not even worth 100 taels of silver.
أنا لا أستحق حتى 100 تيل من الفضة.
Father,
أب،
you're biased.
أنت متحيز.
You rascal.
أنت الوغد.
Is this the time
هل هذا هو الوقت
to think about this?
للتفكير في هذا؟
Yanqing,
يانكينغ ،
what do you think
ماذا تعتقد؟
we should do about this?
يجب أن نفعل حيال هذا؟
From what you said,
مما قلته
you didn't get the questions.
لم تحصل على الأسئلة.
That's not collusion.
هذا ليس تواطؤًا.
That's right.
صحيح.
However,
لكن،
those people have targeted you.
هؤلاء الناس استهدفوك.
They've even got Le's thumbprint as evidence.
لديهم حتى بصمة إبهام لي كدليل.
I'm afraid you can hardly
أخشى أنك بالكاد تستطيع
explain yourselves before His Majesty.
اشرحوا أنفسكم أمام جلالة الملك.
Why not
ولم لا
you do this?
تفعل هذا
We've given
لقد قدمنا
all our asset,
كل أصولنا ،
1,000 taels of gold, to them.
1000 تايل من الذهب لهم.
1,000 taels of gold?
1000 تايل من الذهب؟
I'm thinking
انا افكر
about your father
عن والدك
and your brother.
واخوكم.
Collaborate with me
تعاون معي
and I'll protect Shen family.
وسأحمي عائلة شين.
How does it sound?
كيف يبدو صوته؟
(Is this a scheme?)
(هل هذا مخطط؟)
(It must be the bad guy Xu Yanqing's plan.)
(يجب أن تكون خطة الرجل السيئ شو يانكينغ).
(He's a poke face.)
(إنه وجه وخز).
(He's indeed the most wicked guy in Great Sui.)
(إنه بالفعل أكثر الرجال شراً في Great Sui).
Mother,
الأم،
I'll look for them.
سأبحث عنهم.
No need to look for us.
لا حاجة للبحث عنا.
We're back.
عدنا.